lacrossemonkey.com 2007-06-16

# 

|  | | 

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._ Lacrosse Monkey |  | **** |  |    
---|---|---|---  
| **Yahoo! shopping means Privacy and Security:**  
---  
  
**Credit Card Security  
****We guarantee that you will be able to use your credit card securely while shopping at LacrosseMonkey.com.** Yahoo! Shopping uses the latest browser encryption technologies, which provides the highest level of security currently available and insures secure transactions. All important and private financial & personal information is encrypted before it is transmitted to us. Encrypted personal information can not be read or recorded as it is being transmitted over the internet. **Lacrosse Monkey Privacy Policy**  
At Lacrossemonkey.com, your privacy is a top priority.  Our only goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our services.     
**  
** When you shop on our site, we collect personal information from you such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment types.  
  
We do not sell or rent your personal information to others. We use customer information we collect only for the purposes of filling orders, contacting purchasers to inform them of their order status, sending promotional information (only if requested), enhancing the operation of our site, for statistical purposes and to administer our systems. We may use third parties to help us fulfill orders, to help process payments, to provide customer service, to serve site content, help administer promotional emails, and to administer drawings or contests. We give them access to the information needed to do their job. Sometimes that includes your personal information. Our computer system protects personal information using advanced firewall technology.  **We will not provide, rent, or make available in any way, customer information to any party outside of Lacrosse Monkey.** Customer order information, credit card information and phone numbers are used to process the orders only.  
**  
Yahoo! Shopping Privacy Policy**  
Lacrosse Monkey is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. **Yahoo! Shopping is a TRUST-e certified, meaning that an outside body has certified that Yahoo! Shopping does not improperly use any personal information collected from customers while online.** Please see the [ Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information.  

|   
**The Yahoo! Shopping Merchant Rating system:**  
  
What is the Yahoo! Merchant rating system? The rating system guarantees that the merchants you deal with provide superior customer service. Anyone that does not provide consistently good customer service is not allowed to be a Yahoo! Shopping store. Yahoo! Shopping takes this rating system very seriously. 

The "Top Service" 5-Star logo next to a store's name is a sign of superlative quality.It means that the store is participating in our Customer Rating Program, and that customers who have ordered from that store have given it the highest ratings. Nearly all Yahoo! stores have good customer satisfaction ratings, but those with 5 stars are the best of the best, with at least 95% positive ratings.  
  
**How are merchants rated?**  
---  
The Merchant Rating System is an integral part of Yahoo!'s program to guarantee a positive, high-quality online shopping experience. The rating system gathers feedback from shoppers about Yahoo! Shopping merchants and then uses the feedback to determine an overall rating for that merchant. The system is weighted so that the merchant's overall rating reflects the majority of customer ratings. If most customers rate the store positively, the rating will reflect this. The overall rating is displayed next to the store name whenever it appears in the Yahoo! Shopping pages.

**Be a smart Yahoo! Shopper...**  
Use merchant ratings to make more informed purchasing decisions. And, after you place an order, contribute your feedback by filling out a merchant evaluation form.

 **The Lacrosse Monkey mission:** **  
Provide superior customer service, unparalleled selection, at unbeatable prices!!**  
The superior customer service of Lacrosse Monkey and the peace of mind offered by Yahoo! Shopping is your guarantee that your online shopping experience with Lacrosse Monkey will be a safe, secure, and pleasant one!  
  
| 

Copyright© 1999 - 2007 Monkey Sports, Inc.  
All Rights Reserved. Lacrosse Monkey™ and Lacrossemonkey.com™  
are operated by and are trademarks of Monkey Sports, Inc. [Site Map](http://www.lacrossemonkey.com/site-map.html)   [Contact Us](http://www.lacrossemonkey.com/info.html#contactus)   [Link to Us](http://www.lacrossemonkey.com/link-to-us.html)

Lacrosse Monkey is your source for top quality Lax Equipment offering brands such as: Warrior, Brine, deBeer, Gait, STX, Cascade, Stryke, and many more. Lacrosse Equipment you need, Including Men’s, Women’s and Youth Heads, Shafts, Lacrosse Helmets, Lacrosse Gloves, Lacrosse Elbow Pads, Lacrosse Shoulder Pads, and Cleats at the Lowest Prices. Don’t forget to check our Clearance Section to save up to 80% on select Lacrosse equipment!   
  
---
